<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>golden d6 on The Geek Trading Co.</title>
    <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/tags/golden-d6/</link>
    <description>Recent content in golden d6 on The Geek Trading Co.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://geektradingco.github.io/tags/golden-d6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #01</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue01/</guid>
      <description> The inaugural issue of the world&amp;rsquo;s, possibly, greatest wargames hobby magazine.
ISSUE ONE contents:
 Malifaux hobby log Painting tutorials Making enamel washes Kings of War reviews and battle report Batman Miniatures Game review Scenery tutorials PHAT Models featuring Warpstorm Painting Other cool stuff …  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #02</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue02/</guid>
      <description>The much anticipated second issue of The Golden D6. Six months after Issue One seems like more than enough time to wait for the second issue and I am disgustingly proud and excited for you to finally get a look at it.
In this issue
 Shizune Paints shows us how to paint blue armour Allied Wargaming present Bolt Action for the Hobbyist Evil Nevets painting show off an awesome looking Combined Army Fraacta from Infinity We’re introduced to the cast and crew at Metalhead Minis Haaaaave you met … Andy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #03</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue03/</guid>
      <description>“Only one month? Surely you must be joking?!” “I&amp;rsquo;m not joking and don&amp;rsquo;t call me Shirley!”
The new issue of the Golden D6.
Along with the one and only Queen Bee from Jeff Tibbetts The Golden D6 features:
 A Warhammer 40000 battle report from The Burning Eye Eric the Shed brings us a 28mm Pillbox terrain tutorial An amazing Dwarf Slayer painting tutorial from Kujo Painting Joe Baird&amp;rsquo;s back and this time he&amp;rsquo;s brought monsters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #04</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue04/</guid>
      <description>“Only one month? Surely you must be joking?!” “I&amp;rsquo;m not joking and don&amp;rsquo;t call me Shirley!”
The new issue of the Golden D6.
Along with the one and only Queen Bee from Jeff Tibbetts The Golden D6 features:
 A Warhammer 40000 battle report from The Burning Eye Eric the Shed brings us a 28mm Pillbox terrain tutorial An amazing Dwarf Slayer painting tutorial from Kujo Painting Joe Baird&amp;rsquo;s back and this time he&amp;rsquo;s brought monsters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #05</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue05/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip;
The new issue of the Golden D6.
The Golden D6 Issue Five has a heap of great stuff in it:
 A Fistful of Kung Fu interview with Andrea Sfiligoi An awesome Star Wars Imperial Assault battle report by Matthew Sullivan Guildball review and play guide from Dave at Mini Musings of a Bear Star Wars X-Wing battle report by Ali Ghosn An exclusive Warcolours&amp;rsquo; paint range review by Joe Baird Frostgrave Deadite warband by Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #06</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue06/</guid>
      <description>The Golden D6. Issue Six. 6D6!
It&amp;rsquo;s a dice thing.
In our first big experiment, it&amp;rsquo;s the all tutorial issue. We&amp;rsquo;ve plumbed the depths of the internet to bring you eleven inspiring tutorials!
The Issue contains:
 An air brush maintenance tutorial from Melbourne&amp;rsquo;s own Steve King Painting a Combined army Oznat from Andrew House An Iron Warrior&amp;rsquo;s painting guide from Edd Ralph Display bases for miniatures An awesome Ikea Modular Dungeon Tutorial from Shedwars DIY Gaming Tokens from the #Spruegrey Nation&amp;rsquo;s own Metal Valkyrie from Metalhead Minis Toilet paper terrain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #07</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue07/</guid>
      <description>The Golden D6 Issue Seven is special. Not because it’s the number seven, but more that this represents the one year anniversary of the Golden D6 monthly magazine. Well, nearly monthly. It’s a work in progress.
Thanks to one and all for reading and support I’d like to particularly thank:
 Matt Weaver for his awesome designs Joe Baird, the GD6 OG James Mason for help with the proofreading (any of the mistakes are his fault, not mine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #08</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue08/</guid>
      <description>STOP! DO NOT BUY THIS MAGAZINE Unless …
 You want to learn how to paint Ork skin like a freaking beast thanks to David Colwell You want to learn how to magnetize an Imperial Knight for Warhammer 40000! Better than that, this can be applied to any larger scale model You’re a little bit Malifaux-curious Dishdash Games&amp;rsquo; Zombie survival scenarios are interesting You’re a fan of Rex Foote’s awesome Kings of War narrative battle reports You want to read one of the most complete tree building tutorials ever from Dagger and Brush  Over 100 pages of hobby tutorials, battle reports and reviews designed by the talented Melissa Jones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #09</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue09/</guid>
      <description>Just in time for last minute Chrismas shopping, it&amp;rsquo;s the Golden D6 Issue #9 Featuring:
 Maintenance of reindeer and other live stock A review of Dragon Rampant. Turning Fantasy gaming up to 11! Get your teeth kicked in by a Seraphim. Part two of our feature of the Silver Demon winning “Hammer of Wrath” What to do if you overdose on chocolate Totally #TeamTony. How to paint Knight Model&amp;rsquo;s, Iron Man A fascinating dissertation on the theory of Painting Busts No box can contain Super Dungeon Explore!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #10</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue10/</guid>
      <description>The Golden D6 Issue #10; the Showcase Issue!
Featuring:
 Iron Fate by Thor at Creative Twilight Look Away a zombie diorama by David Colwell Painting the demon&amp;rsquo;s bust by Nils Holmbergh Horus the Warmaster by Rory Priest Zombies In Space by Stats Alexander&amp;rsquo;s Sylvaneth Army Fabius Bile by Joe Baird The Fallen Angel, Cypher by Duane Wood The Witch Queen by Nils Holmbergh Harley Quinn and the Sleeping Chibi by Neil Szabo Part three of Hammer of Wrath by Rory Priest The Warlock of Firetop Mountain diaromma by Stuart Bannister Kingdom Death … after dark by Scott Ferguson  The Golden D6 is designed by the talented Melissa Jones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #11</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue11/</guid>
      <description>The Golden D6 Issue #11 Featuring:
 A painting tutorial by Chris at Nightshade Miniatures Ancient Vaako from Khorne&amp;rsquo;s Eternal Hunt Our cover feature on the Iron Snakes from Marc A T.N.T warband and background from Matt Detail Painting Deathguard from Adpaint Medieval Huts from Oakbound Studio Frostgrave terrain tutorials from Richbuilds.com Malifaux Sky Pirates from Sean Kings of War Drakon Rider conversions from Pawel at Path of an Outcast  The Golden D6 is designed by the talented Melissa Jones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Golden D6 Issue #12</title>
      <link>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geektradingco.github.io/goldend6/issue12/</guid>
      <description>Issue 12 of the Golden D6 features:
 More Dakka den yoo is - A Warhammer 40K Ork Morkanaut painting tutorial from Joe Baird (the Golden D6 OG) A forest basing tutorial from Red Kitana How to become a better painter (in 12 easy steps) by Thor from Creative Twilight How to use laser cut ferns on your miniature&amp;rsquo;s base by Marc van Holst Beardy Bastards - A Warhammer 40K webcomic!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>